ALES Records 5225
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 25)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 26)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 27)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 28)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 29)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 30)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 31)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 32)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 33)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 34)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 35)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 36)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 37)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 38)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 39)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 40)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 41)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 42)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 43)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 44)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 45)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 46)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 47)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 48)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 49)
- Correspondence arid cooperation with labor organizations (Box 57, Folder 50)
- ALES cooperation with government agencies consists mostly of responses to requests for materials (Box 58, Folder 1)
  Includes letters from Secretary of State Dean Rusk and Assistant Secretary of State Merrill expressing confidence in ALES international work. Departments and agencies as follows: U.S. Information Agency, Department of Health Education and Welfare, U.S. Department of Labor-Women's Bureau, International Labor Affairs, U.S. Dept. of State, U.S. National Committee of UNESCO
- ALES cooperation with government agencies consists mostly of responses to requests for materials (Box 58, Folder 2)
- ALES cooperation with government agencies consists mostly of responses to requests for materials (Box 58, Folder 3)
- ALES cooperation with government agencies consists mostly of responses to requests for materials (Box 58, Folder 4)
- ALES cooperation with government agencies consists mostly of responses to requests for materials (Box 58, Folder 5)
- ALES cooperation with government agencies consists mostly of responses to requests for materials (Box 58, Folder 6)
- ALES cooperation with government agencies consists mostly of responses to requests for materials (Box 58, Folder 7)
- ALES cooperation with government agencies consists mostly of responses to requests for materials (Box 58, Folder 8)
- UNESCO and U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 58, Folder 9)
  Coit was a Board Member
- UNESCO and U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 58, Folder 10)
- UNESCO and U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 58, Folder 11)
- UNESCO and U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 58, Folder 12)
- UNESCO and U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 58, Folder 13)
- UNESCO and U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 58, Folder 14)
- UNESCO and U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 58, Folder 15)
- UNESCO and U.S. Committee for the United Nations (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 17)
  for the following universities: University of California-Los Angeles, University of California-Berkeley, Chicago University, Colgate University, Columbia University, Cornell University, Fisk University, Harvard University, University of Illinois, Michigan State University, University of Minnesota, New York University, Pennsylvania State University, Purdue University, Roosevelt University, Rutgers University, Smith College, University of Wisconsin
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 18)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 19)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 20)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 21)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 22)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 23)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 24)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 25)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 26)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 27)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 28)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 29)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 30)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 31)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 32)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 33)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 34)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 35)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 36)
- Contacts and advisory services (Box 58, Folder 37)
- University program for foreign trade unionists, includes Coit's survey on programs available (Box 58, Folder 38)
- Adult Education Association (AEA) correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Adult Education Association (AEA) correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Adult Education Association (AEA) correspondence, 1957-1959 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- AEA, Malcolm Knowles, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- AEA, miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 5)
- AEA, Executive Committee, 1950-1954 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  Coit was Board member and active in formation and direction of this section, speeches, correspondence, committees, and Cincinnati Conference
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- AEA, Labor Education Section, 1957-1962 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- AEA, Social Philosophy and Direction Finding Committee, correspondence (Box 59, Folder 17)
  re trends in thinking on adult education
- AEA, Social Philosophy and Direction Finding Committee, correspondence (Box 59, Folder 18)
- AEA, Social Philosophy and Direction Finding Committee, correspondence (Box 59, Folder 19)
- AEA, Social Philosophy and Direction Finding Committee, correspondence (Box 59, Folder 20)
- AEA, Social Philosophy and Direction Finding Committee, correspondence (Box 59, Folder 21)
- AEA, Social Philosophy and Direction Finding Committee, correspondence (Box 59, Folder 22)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1962 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1942 (Box 59, Folder 25)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1932 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1922 (Box 59, Folder 27)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1912 (Box 59, Folder 28)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1902 (Box 59, Folder 29)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1892 (Box 59, Folder 30)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1882 (Box 59, Folder 31)
- AEA, Council of National Organizations, financial data, program, by-laws, minutes and budgets, 1951-1872 (Box 59, Folder 32)
- New York State AEA, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 33)
- Ford Foundation, correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 59, Folder 34)
- Ford Foundation, projects (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Ford Foundation, projects (Box 59, Folder 36)
- Ford Foundation, projects (Box 59, Folder 37)
- Ford Foundation, projects (Box 59, Folder 38)
- Ford Foundation, projects (Box 59, Folder 39)
- Ford Foundation, projects (Box 59, Folder 40)
- Ford Foundation, correspondence, 1952-1961 (Box 59, Folder 41)
- Ford Foundation, correspondence, 1952-1961 (Box 59, Folder 42)
- Ford Foundation, releases and announcements, 1952-1962 (Box 59, Folder 43)
- Ford Foundation, releases and announcements, 1952-1962 (Box 59, Folder 44)
- New York Educational Council (Box 59, Folder 45)
- New York Educational Council (Box 59, Folder 46)
- Committee on Autonomous Groups (Box 59, Folder 47)
- Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (Box 60, Folder 1)
  includes "Citizen Activity in World Affairs" conference
- Foreign Policy Association and FPA's World Affairs Center, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  exchange of materials, advice on international labor contacts
- Foreign Policy Association and FPA's World Affairs Center, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Foreign Policy Association and FPA's World Affairs Center, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- American Association of the United Nations, 1952-1961 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- American Association of the United Nations, 1952-1961 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- American Association of the United Nations, 1952-1961 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- American Association of the United Nations, 1952-1961 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- American Association of the United Nations, 1952-1961 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- United Nations (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Council on World Affairs, 1953-1955 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Council on World Affairs, 1953-1955 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  a committee of women active in international affairs to encourage contacts and meet needs of world women leaders, correspondence, African seminar and other seminar programs, agendas and minutes of meetings
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 27)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 28)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 30)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 31)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 32)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 33)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 34)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 35)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 36)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 37)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 38)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 39)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 40)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 41)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 42)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 43)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 44)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 45)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 46)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 60, Folder 47)
- ALES Committee on International Exchange, 1950-1954 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- ALES Committee on International Exchange, 1950-1954 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- ALES Committee on International Exchange, 1950-1954 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- ALES Committee on International Exchange, 1950-1954 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- ALES Committee on International Exchange, 1950-1954 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- ALES Committee on International Exchange, 1950-1954 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- ALES Committee on International Exchange, 1950-1954 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Conference Board of Association of Research Councils, Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1950-1958 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Conference Board of Association of Research Councils, Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1950-1958 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Conference Board of Association of Research Councils, Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1950-1958 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Selection Committee on Fulbright Awards, 1952-1959 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Other foreign scholarships (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Other foreign scholarships (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Ruskin College, Oxford, scholarships, student comments, descriptive material, 1951-1958 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Ruskin College, Oxford, scholarships, student comments, descriptive material, 1951-1958 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Ruskin College, Oxford, scholarships, student comments, descriptive material, 1951-1958 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Ruskin College, Oxford, scholarships, student comments, descriptive material, 1951-1958 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Ruskin College, Oxford, scholarships, student comments, descriptive material, 1951-1958 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Ruskin College, Oxford, scholarships, student comments, descriptive material, 1951-1958 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Ruskin College, Oxford, scholarships, student comments, descriptive material, 1951-1958 (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Ruskin College, Oxford, scholarships, student comments, descriptive material, 1951-1958 (Box 61, Folder 29)
- American-Scandinavian Foundation (Box 61, Folder 30)
- Scandinavian-ALES awards, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 31)
- English Speaking Union (Box 61, Folder 32)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 33)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 34)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 35)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 36)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 37)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 38)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 39)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 40)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 41)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 42)
- Institute of International Exchange, correspondence, conferences, studies, and reports, 1953-1961 (Box 61, Folder 43)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 1)
  arranged alphabetically by the following countries: Africa (Kenya), Australia, Austria, Belgium (Brussels), British West Indies, Burma, Canada, Denmark (includes women trade unionists), England (Includes women trade unionists), France, Bermany, Italy, (women trade unionists), Iran, Japan, Jordan, Lebanon, Mexico, Netherlands, New Zealand, Norway, Pakistan, Philippines, Puerto Rico, Scotland, South America
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 18)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 19)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 20)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 21)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 22)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 23)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 25)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 26)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 27)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 28)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 29)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 30)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 31)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 32)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 33)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 34)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 35)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 36)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 37)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 38)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 39)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 40)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 41)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 42)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 43)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 44)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 45)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 46)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 47)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 48)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 49)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 50)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 51)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 52)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 53)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 54)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 55)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 56)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 57)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 58)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 59)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 60)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 61)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 62)
- Foreign guests, includes schedules, programs planned for visitors (Box 62, Folder 63)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Singapore, Sweden, Thailand (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Card file of foreign visitors, A-N (Box 63, Folder 17)
- Card file of foreign visitors, D-Z (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Foreign advisory, 1950-1958 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- General, 1958-1962 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- General, 1958-1962 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- General, 1958-1962 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- General, 1958-1962 (Box 65, Folder 5)